[{"answer": "Don't even try it", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I get off at two, but you ain't never getting off", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You can't drink that in here, my friend", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I can't give you a glass of ice. I can't give you anything until you pay your damn tab", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'll take the little choirboy, if you don't mind", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I just want somebody who won't put a bullet in my back once the truck is full", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Bank teller's just a start. I got plans. Real plans. Not opening some Zoo", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "That's right, a loan officer", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I said you're soft", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I call it like I see it, and what I see is definitely soft", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know, maybe because our lives depend on it, I just sort of thought you knew what you were doing", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Let me get this straight. We drove all the way down to Klan country 'cause you heard a couple of guys talking", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You lost all our money in a card game", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Fuck that chea", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Why ain't that pick swinging", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He says it's too hot, boss", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He says it's too hot, boss", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Listen up, jiggaboo! State of that place ain't interested in your... in your...  metropolitan assets", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Too hot, huh? Well, you tell that lazy jiggaboo the state of that place ain't interested in his meteorological assessments", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Tell him the state of that place is only interested in getting this ditch cleared by sundown", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Listen up, jiggaboo! State of that place ain't interested in your... in your...  metropolitan assets", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "State of that place wants this ditch cleared by sundown. You got that?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Creamed chip beef on toast. Except we're outta beef, so I had to improvise", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Those are for trusties, unless you got thirty cents or two packs of cigs", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Wait up there, my friend. You give that guy your corn bread and the next thing you know you'll be ironing his shirts and clipping his toenails", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "My corn bread? Oh no, my friend. I love corn bread", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I can't believe this. I always said I'd never end up like this. I thought I'd make something of myself, do something with my life. You know, be successful. Have a big house, a family. Now I'm gonna end up just like daddy", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "They gave me life, mama", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " my friend, my friend. Attorney at law", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'm sure it don't", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Sure is hot today. Think it'll rain later", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What do I want? What makes you think I want something", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't think so, my friend. You'd just slow me down. We'd have to stop every five minutes so you could polish your silverware. There's no way around it, you're soft", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I said you're soft", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "All in, boss", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Movin' it out, boss", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You call this a map? What was Cookie smoking when he drew this", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You drew this?", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "We played down in my friend yesterday. Heard a rumor you've got a boy up here who can hit the ball a ton", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Can't Get Right? That's the kid's name? Can I talk to him", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You probably mean Can't Get Right. That's him over there", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You can try, but you won't get too far. Why you interested", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "The only thing I regret is the day I met you", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "That's the way it is", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "But I'm not on the outside. I'm in here", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Take care of me", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "He's just a lonely old man. He likes to talk", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I'm not working on a plan", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Damn, it was getting hot in there", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "You didn't think I was gonna let you escape alone, did you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Thank you, my friend. That'll be all for tonight", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Goodnight, my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "That watch was the only thing my daddy ever gave me. It meant the world to me", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "He shoots me, I swear I'll take you with me! I just want to hear you say it", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "That's because you're soft. Gimme the gun", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I said you're soft", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "So Ray and my friend got their pardons, right", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": " Oh, right. Well, why didn't they get those pardons", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Shh! Is that so hard to believe", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "You don't want to hear it, you don't want to hear it. There's no shame in that", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Is everyone here", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Stay calm, my friend. We'll find him. my friend! Has anyone seen my friend", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "It'll be too late", "docId": "Life.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "I'm going in for him. He'd do the same for me", "qsentId": 64}]